One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
The Royal Palace Floor B-1
(Outer Wall Tower)
Usoland the Liar
There are dead ends all over the place.
I told you, Pica has complete control over this stone castle.
Straw Hat, will he really be okay?
Huh? Zoro?
You don't need to worry about him.
Zoro'll be fine no matter what happens.
On the same floor –
Zoro vs. Pica
He's still undamaged.
This guy just won't quit!
How do I even attack him?
The Royal Palace
First Floor –
The Soldier and
the Dwarves
Captain! It's another officer!
That's Gladius from the Pica Army!
You don't stand a chance as you are now.
Ranpo and I will distract him.
Keep moving while he's occupied!
Stop! Do you plan to sacrifice yourselves?
Ranpo!
Let's attack from both sides, Kabu-san!
Yes!
Wait!
Why do I have to fight these mice?
Kabu!
Ranpo!
I know toys aren't that fast.
I'm a rupture man who ate the Pamu Pamu Fruit.
I can make my own body burst...
as well as...
any non-organic material I touch.
I can easily blow a tin toy like you to smithereens!
Let go of me!
I have to...
fulfill my mission!
Rebecca!
Rupture and die!
Jet Stamp!
Who's there?!
Soldier, where are Franky and the others?
You're...
What, they're not with you?
Straw Hat, we don't have time to chat!
Straw Hat Luffy?
Violet?!
How dare you...
How dare you betray the young master!
Bring it on!
No, run!
What?
There's no time. Besides, he's exceedingly dangerous.
We have to hurry to the Suit Chamber on the second floor!
Viola-sama, why are you here?
You know me?
Yes, though you don't remember me.
I've been watching you with my Clairvoyance the whole time.
Both you and Rebecca.
It must have been hard for you. Thank you.
Violet!
You, traitorous woman...
must die!
I haven't betrayed anyone!
These past ten years, I've never once been on your side!
Still, you've disgraced the young master!
Helmet Puncture!
Viola-sama!
Oh no!
Hey, you're gonna be okay, aren't you?
Sorry, I should have protected you.
I just have to keep going, right?
Wait!
The stairs aren't this way!
What?!
Where are you going?!
Up there, right?
Where did they go?
Young master? What are you doing here?
Kin'emon In Disguise
Donquixote Doflaemon
"Young master"?
I am Donqui-
They call Doflamingo "young master"!
I am the young master.
There are intruders in the palace.
Please wait upstairs until we dispose of them.
No, that I cannot do.
You take care of things here.
I must go check on Kanjuurou below.
The samurai who vanished from the scrap yard?
What?
He vanished?!
A-Amazing! We're right in front of our goal!
Royal Palace Second Floor
The Suit Chamber
Why are we hiding?
Mingo's right there!
Be quiet.
You'll ruin their entire operation.
Operation?
I thought you were only after the Smile factory.
Isn't that right?
So why are Straw Hats and the dwarves from Green Bit working together?
That's not an alliance you could have just formed on a whim one day.
Dwarves?
How did they get underground?
Why are they after Sugar?
What is the meaning of their actions?
All these inconveniences are piling up on top of each other.
Unless this is a coincidence, then they...
must know the dark roots of this kingdom.
Answer! The young master asked you a question, Law!
Don't hit him if it makes you cry -dasuyan.
You never change.
But...
Didn't I tell you?
They have nothing to do with me anymore.
Our alliance is broken.
I don't even understand most of what you're talking about.
If only Violet were with me for this interrogation. She could get the truth out of you immediately.
Or...
This can't be your doing, can it, King Riku?
The Tontattans used to serve you too.
Father, what are you doing in the palace?
Traf is still alive.
King Riku! It's so good to see you safe after all these years!
Your name is Kyros? Come with me.
I swear I'll save you!
Aren't Leo and the others done yet?
Once I and the other toys in Dressrosa return to human form...
that will be my only chance to kill Doflamingo!
I will kill him!
I can't let Kabu and Ranpo's sacrifice be in vain!
I'm counting on you, Leo and Usoland!
Toys' House
Give it up, Franky!
Stop resisting and turn yourself in!
Shut up.
Shut the hell up!
I've decided to go on a pointless rampage, so prepare yourselves.
If I went underground with these guys after me, I'd get in the dwarves' way.
I'll leave Operation SOP to you guys.
Bring it on!
I'll take on these guys.
I'm counting on you, Usoland.
Underground Trading Port –
Remains of the Officers' Tower
What on earth is going on over there?
Apparently there's an intruder.
But we've got Trebol-sama on our side.
I feel bad for them, but they don't stand a chance against him.
They just keep getting back up.
I let my guard down and was made into a toy.
That means that everyone must have forgotten about me.
Usopp...
Where's Usopp?
You can do it, Usopp.
You're the only one left.
Turn me back into a human.
They were trying so hard to make me eat this.
It's probably poison.
It stinks.
W-We can't do anything anymore.
Don't worry! If anything goes wrong, I'll save you!
Usoland.
Move it!
Where are you going, buddy?
Alright, I've successfully escaped!
Forgive me, Tontattans.
Usopp, where are you?
Okay, I'll write of your bravery in a
picture book for future generations.
"The Trusting Tontattans." That's a good title.
I must live on.
Besides, this is all Franky's fault.
Why won't he come help?
Like hell I'm dying for the sake of pretending to be a hero!
Now that I've escaped, how do I get out of here?
I can't use the hole we came in from on my own.
Wait, they said there's a port.
Hey, everyone outside!
Hey, hey, are you guys working?
This isn't some show, you bastards!
Oh crap!
Get back to work!
Keep moving those crates!
Don't just stand there!
Hurry the hell up!
Is someone standing up to the Donquixote Family?
It's been eight years since I became a toy, and this is a first.
I don't care who, but please destroy this place!
A show?! I've seen enough of it!
What are we gonna do about them?
Hey, hey, are these guys saying something?
Uso...
... la...
... nd.
... land.
Usoland.
Usola...
Dammit, where's the lift?!
Usoland.
Usoland?
That's the name he said before.
Usoland... Usoland... Usoland...
Uso...
Usoland!
Usoland?
Dammit, don't call my name!
Usoland? Hey, who's that?
Like I said, it's the name the dwarves said earlier.
You're an idiot. Just die.
As if I'd die, you damn brat.
Usoland is our hero.
H-H-Hero?
Then he's gonna come save you all?
That's right.
And not just us.
Usoland said he'd save us all.
The toys who are forced to work everyday down here.
Is he talking about us?
Our comrades who are slaving away in the factory.
The toys who look cheerful walking through town as they cry inside.
The poor big folk who don't realize they've lost someone dear to them.
Usoland's gonna save us all.
He's a legendary hero!
Like hell I'm gonna pretend to be a hero!
Poor you.
He was lying all along.
Were you guys deceived again?
Are you telling the truth?
You're all about to die, and he still hasn't shown up. That's all the proof you need.
Where's the hero?
Well? Where?
But he said he'd save us.
He's probably somewhere laughing at how stupid you all are.
You guys are way too trusting.
And if this isn't some dream you made up,
and he really did say he'd save everyone, then he's the kind of guy who
runs away in the face of danger.
Just throw away all hope!
I hate to say it, but he's mostly right.
You guys run away too. Good luck.
Th-That can't be...
Shut up!
Usoland would never tell a lie!
Usoland is...
I'm Noland's descendant!
Amazing!
No matter what, Usoland will definitely save us.
That's what he told us!
That's right.
That's right! That's right! That's right!
He promised us.
A hero would never deceive us!
If you keep besmirching Usoland's name,
you'll regret it.
You should prepare yourselves.
When Usoland comes, you won't-
What a funny scream.
The Tontattans have such a funny death cry.
Leo!
That's right. It's as Leo says.
Usoland will complete Operation SOP!
That's right.
You should feel sorry for yourselves, not us!
Then hurry up and call him, your hero.
How cruel is he?!
Stop it, just stop!
Just give it a rest already!
Usoland!
Usopp!
I'm so glad.
Just how long are you gonna believe in me, you idiotic dwarves?!
It's just as he said, it was all a lie.
I'm not a legendary hero, and Usoland isn't my name.
I'm the sniper from the Straw Hat Pirates!
My name is Usopp!
I'm a pirate!
Th-The Straw Hat Pirates?
Why are they down here?
Why...
Why would you say that?
You may be a pirate, but you're still a hero, right?
I told you, no!
A pirate is a pirate!
Don't make me keep repeating myself!
I was lying to you all!
And you just kept believing me!
So you came all the way here just to say it was a lie?
If I didn't, these guys would keep waiting until they died.
If that happened, I could never live with myself.
Since they insist on believing in me so much,
I'll have to do the cool thing and risk my life to save them!
My name is Usopp!
Remember it well, Tontattans!
If I die, then build me a statue beside Noland's!
I'm about to become your legendary hero!
Usopp!
Usopp, from the Straw Hat Pirates.
Is he gonna be the one to save us?
How desperate.
It's all or nothing!
Sure-Kill Green Star: Platanus...
...Shuriken!
How's that, you monster?!
I'm the legendary hero, the Straw Hat Pirates' sniper, Captain Usopp!
Usoland!
It's Usopp!
I said it's Usopp!
The legendary hero, Usoland!
It's been reported that you were on the first floor, young master.
Royal Palace, Second Floor
The Suit Chamber
What's that supposed to mean?
King Riku...
This is a fine sword.
If I become human again, I'll use this.
My father fought in the Colosseum today.
What? Really?
When he learned that the news of
Doflamingo's abdication was incorrect,
he couldn't take it anymore, just like the rest of us.
King Riku was at the Colosseum?!
A young boy has committed murder!
Two people were killed in a scuffle in the slums!
Boy from the slums
Kyros (15 years old)
Your Majesty!
What are you doing, Your Majesty?
It's too dangerous!
He may be a child, but his bad reputation has spread throughout the country!
His Majesty is in danger! Shoot the boy!
No, don't shoot!
Lower your weapons!
B-But, Sir...
I understand you fought alone against dozens of opponents.
Over half of them were injured, and two of them...
They killed my best friend.
I was just paying them back!
Are you a beast?
Call me whatever you like!
You royals don't understand anything!
He was the only one in this world I could trust!
He was like a brother to me.
Your name is Kyros, right?
Come with me.
A fifteen-year-old killer, Kyros!
Corrida Colosseum
His opponent is a veteran gladiator!
This is a sacred Colosseum!
What talent! If that blade had been sharp, his opponent would've died instantly!
Outside they call it "brutality", but in here it's "talent", huh?
He effortlessly beat his cell mates half to death.
He's gone six days without eating,
continuously shouting for us to call you.
What do you want with me, King Riku?!
King Riku is saying that if you can win a hundred battles,
he will grant you a parole.
It doesn't matter how many years it takes.
Four months later
At last, Kyros stands at a hundred battles and a hundred victories!
He's put even our biggest stars to shame!
Don't go back out, murderer!
You won't leave?
I won't go where I'm not wanted.
When did you start caring about being wanted?
Shut it!
Beasts...
can only be appreciated...
inside their cages!
Two hundred victories!
Somebody, defeat Kyros!
Take him down!
Three hundred victories!
None can stop Kyros!
The heroes keep falling before him!
At last... At last...
The fourth year
in the Colosseum
he is the first man to ever...
win a thousand battles straight!
Kyros-sama!
You go, Kyros!
You've come here again?
Stay back!
How could you understand?
No matter what I do,
I'll always be a murderer and a beast!
Is there...
no way...
they could forget me?